They threatened his world. He will destroy theirs.
Braven is a drama, action, thriller film directed by Lin Oeding.
A logger defends his family from a group of dangerous drug runners.
Joe Braven, played by Jason Momoa.
Linden, played by Stephen Lang.
Kassen, played by Garret Dillahunt.
Hallett, played by Zahn McClarnon.
Stephanie, played by Jill Wagner.
Weston, played by Brendan Fletcher.
Braven is a 2018 action thriller film directed by Lin Oeding and
written by Mike Nilon and Thomas Pa'a Sibbett.
The film stars Jason Momoa as Joe Braven, with Garret Dillahunt,
Stephen Lang, Jill Wagner, and Brendan Fletcher.
Principal photography began in December 2015 in Newfoundland, Canada.
Scenes for this film were also shot and included from Springhill, Nova Scotia.
The film was released on February 2, 2018.
The film explores themes of drug dealer, cocaine, log cabin.
The tone is emotional and intense.